<resources>
  <string name="app_name">career-portfolio</string>
  
  <string name="Reflections">
    // Reflections from the Java | Android | Salesforce cohort 4
Week1
    So excited to get to class early every day. Everything is new and it seems like right now
    there is the biggest mountain before me that I\'ve ever had to climb.
    Every night my brain is spinning trying to learn the new concepts and grasp everything
    I\'ve been exposed to thus far. I Feel like a monkey trying to play chess.
Week2
    The excitement is building each and every day. I\'m becoming vaguely more familiar with the concepts.
    My syntax is still really shaky. I can\'t write any Java without my hand being held. I am struggling
    with even the most basic of things. This is a different style of learning that\'s not inherently comfortable.
    This is a challenging environment built to test our ability to focus, learn, and adapt.
    I\'m loving to opportunity to learn new skills and this really seems like an environment where you
    are rewarded for problem solving, critical thinking, and ability to continuously improve.
Week3
    This week has been most Confusing and sometimes discouraging, I feel like I\'m not grasping the material
    at a level that I should be or as quickly as I\'m used to in other subjects. My focus has been on buttoning down and working even harder.
    I have been working on Reading, Practicing, and Classroom time from sun up to sun down.
Week4
    Desert of Despair. I realize that I\'ve got so much to learn and will never have the time to learn
    as much as I want to. It would literally take me lifetimes worth of time dedicated to nothing
    but coding and learning and even then I still wouldn't be able to keep up with just the new changes
    and technologies that are out there. I also realize I could be training for a job 5 years into
    the future that doesn't even exist today.
Week5
    Last week Friday we were given our first test, which consisted of the following 3 practical programming problems:
    1.) Clock Angles
    2.) Staircase
    3.) Leaderboard

Working from sunrise to sunset on coding, also dreaming about code, even in dreams I'm not very good at coding yet.
    I'm able to complete some CodingBat challenges now. Becomming slightly more familiar with Java Every Day.
    We starting learning about Back-end Java programming. We've used Spring and Derby so far.
    The back-end seems marginally easier than front-end for now. Perhaps simply because we haven't
    gone too deep into it yet.
    We started learning about Multi-Threaded programming in Java. This is a pretty tough concept to
    grasp.
    "</string>

  <string name="Qualitative_and_Quantitative">

    ********3 quantitative accomplishments********************
Utilized Salesforce to drive Revenue Increase of 125% YOY - Critical Thinking
Obtained Originator License, DE, BS, - Attention to Detail
Developed a Tickler System to manage sales lead pipeline. - Creativity


********3 qualitative features****************************
Worked in a large team of unrelated parties trying to accomplish the same goal every day. - Teamwork and Communication
Mentored co-workers and teammates who had questions or needed help. - Empathize
  </string>

  <string name="Creativity_Logic">
    ****Write a paragraph on how you balance your creativity and logic in your passion projects.*****

For logic I like to read a lot about new and interesting subjects. I have a beginners mindset in that I can always
    learn something new or
Subjects that interest me are Technology, Computer Science, Astronomy, Physics, Philosophy, All the Science.
For creativity I like to practic Jiu-Jitsu, Archery, and Painting.
  </string>

  <string name="Elevator_Pitch">
    My name is Justin Torrez. I\'m a student at Deep Dive Coding Utilizing new technologies to benefit people.

I\'m interested in helping people to save time by reducing the amount of decisions and or errors in their everyday lives.

After the Cohort I'd like to learn more about AI and Machine Learning. What are you working on?
  </string>

</resources>
